So just if you could comment on your confidence on the peak cells here.
Yeah, thanks, Thibault.
So no change, I'd say, as you know, I just got the European Commission approval.
I think in general with gene therapy as we learned with Zolgensma, it does take some
time to get the reimbursement.
But once we get the reimbursement, we see a relatively steady growth.
So thanks, Tih.
relatively rapid ramp on on the product so we I would say over the three-year
period is where we would expect to see the ramp on in this month as we get
additional countries online it's also worth noting for as with little gents
well we expect X us to be larger than the u.s. same dynamics we saw that with
little gents month so all on track but it is important to note this first year
will be mostly focused on securing reimbursement and you know from a peak
sales potential also no change was old gents mo we expect the continued steady
state in this blockbuster billion-dollar-plus territory and we
expected businessmen to have a kind of two billion dollar range so that the
overall package of these two medicines have a three billion dollar potential
thank you thank you your next question comes from the line of Steve Scala from
TD Capital
and please go ahead thank you so much you called out to Hence how in non U.S.
markets as a growth opportunity but to help to have leadership and nine to ten
markets in q4 and q1 and eight of ten markets in q2 and one difference
appears to have been China so i'm curious what happened with consent to in
China in q2 thank you yes the so-so no change in China that we're aware
aware of. We did drop off in Italy, actually, from 9 out of 10 to 8 out of 10. I'd say in general,
you know, Cosimta does very well in Asia. It's a market leader in Japan. But it is worth noting
that multiple sclerosis levels in Asia are significantly lower than what we see in other
parts of the world. So the overall sales potential is lower. But I would say overall,
we continue to see significant opportunity, you know, outside of the U.S., just simply because
the market has not, you know, B-cell therapies have just not adequately penetrated the market,
you know, outside of the U.S. So for all B-cell therapies, there's just an opportunity to get
more patients on the best possible medicine. And I don't have the details on the Italy